https://newenergyandfuel.com/privacy-policy-3/

New Energy and Fuel
News and Views for Making and Saving Money in New Energy and Fuel
Privacy Policy
New Energy and Fuel takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. See this privacy policy primer to learn more about privacy policies in general.
Routine Information Collection
All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.
Cookies and Web Beacons
Where necessary, New Energy and Fuel uses cookies to store information about a visitor's preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.
Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.
Controlling Your Privacy
Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. This list of web browser privacy management links may also be useful.
Special Note About Google Advertising
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies.
Contact Information
Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to manager@newenergyandfuel.com for further clarification.
This privacy policy was generated by the Privacy Policy for WordPress plugin.
Feedburner
Subscribe in a reader
Reddit
Like This? - For Facebook.
Google +1
Stumbleupon
Recent Comments
Anglena Rossie on A New Idea Using the Deep Ocean Pressure to Store EnergyAries on Treating Biomass With Plasma For BiofuelStarter Battery on Sodium Battery Solid Electrolyte DevelopmentAries on Almost Free Energy That Might Work OutAlisha Ross on A Flow Cell Battery Installed In Prototype Super Car
Recent Posts
A New State of Matter For High Temperature Superconductors
One More Step Closer to Organic Thermoelectric Material
New Research Method Called “Genomic” Improves Batteries
Someday Electrical Power Could Come From Your Clothes
Safer Cheaper Nuclear Fuel Production Worked Out
Copyright © 2007 Thru 2019 New Energy and Fuel • Powered by WordPress • Using Blue Zinfandel 2.0 theme by Brian Gardner • Supported by Doreo Hosting Affordable Reliable Solutions
